Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The first round of the Royal Knight Selection Exam is heating up.
Asta's Team B, Magna's Team C, Finral's Team E, and Longris's Team G have each been successful in their initial matches and secured their spots in the second round.
It's too bad that you'll never be anything more than a means of transport, but my magic is useful.
So do try to stay out of my portals during the next battle. It would be a shame if you were to permanently disappear somewhere.
Forget about what it would do to mother and father, I think a certain someone would be quite devastated as well.
Yeah, good point.
So if I want to prevent that, then I'll just have to win.
Thank you.
Now then, let's move on to match five of the starting round.
Sweet.
Here we go.
Hurry up already.
Members of Team I and Team J, approach.
May the best fighters win.
Let's have a fair match.
I agree.
This should be fun.
We plan to do our best.
Roland, Wainsley, Nyx, Nils, Ruben.
Why is there an X though?
I guess somebody went home.
I'm fairly certain X is someone's name.
Really?
Kinda unusual.
A pseudonym?
I'm sorry.
One question.
What is it?
We're supposed to be on a team with this X, but we don't know who that is.
Is that person even here?
I don't understand what the holdup is.
Find your third team member or you'll be disqualified.
Uh, right.
If the magic knight X is present, then please step forward so that we can proceed.
X?
Whoa!
What's with this guy?
I am the X you seek.
Just kidding.
It was me, Captain Real Boy Mortier.
You guys should have seen your faces.
It's Real, the Aqua Deer Captain.
Why's he here?
I'm confused.
Isn't that the little guy who can transform other people's magic power into paint using his picture magic?
Yeah, why would there be a captain here?
That's weird.
Wait!
Don't tell me there's a rule against captains participating in the exam!
That's not the case at all.
You are welcome here.
Perfect!
Now I get to see Real's magic as well.
Everyone's accounted for, so we can do it.
I don't think we can do it.
We can do it.
Wait!
Don't tell me there's a rule against captains participating in the exam!
That's not the case at all.
You are welcome here.
Perfect!
Now I get to see Real's magic as well.
Everyone's accounted for, so get on with it.
No need to worry, competitors.
Think of this as your chance to make a strong impression by defeating a captain.
He's right.
Yeah.
And the way this competition is set up, we might actually have a decent shot.
I'm doing this to give the Aqua Deer a rankings boost after we came in last at the Star Festival,
so you'd better believe I'm not going to go down without a fight today.
Such determination!
You're a great inspiration, young master.
I'm quite moved.
Now we got Grandpa's flying in out of nowhere!
Everyone, I implore you to look kindly upon Real during this competition.
Oh, Walt, stop being so stuffy.
Hey, it's Asta!
Hmm?
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
But I'm definitely going to beat you!
Don't speak to a captain so casually!
Are you guys friends or something?
Okay, the old geezer's starting to scare me!
Ah, and I assume you must be the young master's dear friend, Asta.
I must say he has spoken very highly of you.
Where'd that cup come from?
It happened so fast!
Words cannot express how deeply I appreciate the companionship you have shown, Master Rill.
But forgive me, for I have yet to introduce myself.
My name is Walter, his humble and dedicated servant.
Please accept this.
Oh, okay, don't mind if I do then.
This is...
What, Asta?
It's so fancy I can't even taste it!
Moron.
Oh my!
I'm so glad to see he's finally found a friend.
Not long ago such a thing would have been unthinkable.
Wow, seriously?
I'm sorry, that sounds like it would be rough.
Please do forgive my rudeness.
I cannot help it.
This is all so touching.
Cut it out, Walt!
Don't talk about the past!
Don't you know it's embarrassing?
Right.
I beg your pardon, Master.
It's time to continue!
All right!
I can't wait to paint my neck here yet, my shirt.
I'm sorry, that sounds like it would be rough.
Please do forgive my rudeness.
I cannot help it.
This is all so touching.
Cut it out, Walt.
Don't talk about the past.
Don't you know it's embarrassing?
Right. I beg your pardon, Master.
It's time to continue!
All right.
I can't wait to paint my next masterpiece.
What does he mean, masterpiece?
The fifth match of round one!
Team I, Rill, Nils, and Ruben
versus Team J, Wainsley, Roland, and Nix!
We're facing the captain of the Aqua Deer.
I wonder what he's like.
Master Rill.
Begin the battle!
I'm sorry, sir. What are you doing?
They just said go.
The sky looks so pretty.
I bet you I can get that exact color
if I use lapis lazuli.
You can create blue paint by crushing up gemstones.
Interesting, right?
Oh.
Then I'll add in a little whitewash for the clouds.
Whitewash is a special kind of paint
that's made out of seashells,
in case you didn't know.
Wow, I couldn't ask for a more beautiful skyscape
for us to compete under today.
All right, team.
I'm ready when you are.
I'm about to paint a marvelous picture
on the inviting blank canvas
that is our battle deal.
Follow my lead, okay?
Here we go!
He just up and left us.
I admire his initiative, but that's too much.
Oh, no!
He captured me!
They're like five seconds in,
and he already screwed up!
And this boy is a captain?
Oh, dear.
He was so busy daydreaming about the sky
that he walked directly into a trap.
Well, this match is going to be fairly brief.
I didn't expect him to be that easy to catch.
I actually feel kind of guilty.
He is a captain, after all.
It doesn't matter a win is a win.
We should face our foes with our full might
no matter how unthreatening they are.
Right.
Works for me.
Here goes!
I'll use Plant Reinforcement Magic Magic Pollen!
Your turn!
All right, Flame Magic.
Flame Spike Technique!
I'll finish this.
Ice Magic Icicle Bridge!
Take that, Captain of the Aqua Tier!
You're going down!
Wow.
Their spells are exquisite,
and they know just how to use them.
This battlefield really is the ideal canvas.
I'm so inspired!
I feel my creativity starting to flow, Walt!
Not again.
How many times is that today?
It's practically constant.
Ever since the boy Mortier Child received his grimoire,
he's been holed up in his room,
allowing his magic to run wild.
I know he's always been a bit of a strange little boy,
but since the awarding ceremony,
he almost seems to be possessed.
Right.
And with that enormous amount of power he's wielding,
he's impossible to control.
I hear his poor mother is at her wit's end.
How could my son have become such a terror?
My lady, please calm yourself.
I can't get him to listen to a single word I say.
All he does is paint all day long.
My sweet boy.
I don't even understand him anymore.
He's a monster!
It's wrong.
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
I hate this.
It isn't what I wanted to paint at all.
It should be more.
More.
Please stop painting now, Rill.
How can you cause me so much pain?
I almost wish.
Now I do wish.
I wish you'd never been born.
You don't understand my art, and you never will.
Never.
Ever.
Young master, may I have a word with you?
Shut up, Walter.
Get out!
But, sir...
Just go!
Why can't I paint the way I want?
Art's supposed to be fun.
This is boring!
Everybody leave me alone!
They have no idea how much I'm suffering.
Not Walter, not Mother, no one!
None of you understand me!
That's good.
It's a relief that you're finally able to see me properly, young master Rill.
What?
Is your face hurting?
When someone sustains an injury, it causes pain.
That's the reason people are so afraid of getting hurt.
We tend to be frightened of what we fail to understand,
so we are reluctant to draw close to such things.
That's why you should try to understand others,
so that they can understand you, too.
You love to make art.
Don't you want someone else to see it as well?
Although a tiny canvas such as this cannot hope to contain your outstanding talent, young master,
your abilities are far too great.
It must be difficult to get the people in your life to understand you.
That's the way it is for those who shine as brightly as you do.
Uh...
But I know of a canvas where you can unleash your colorful magic power to your heart's content.
Huh?
Where's that?
Join the Magic Knights.
The Magic Knights, huh?
Yes.
Would you like to give it a try?
After all, with impressive abilities like yours, you're sure to be accepted.
And then, you'll be free to paint upon the never-ending canvas that spreads out along your path.
You'll create a masterpiece like no other.
Do you really think I can do that, Walt?
Indeed.
Well then, I'm gonna go for it.
Hmm.
Oh, sorry for hurting you. Are you okay?
It's just a scratch, sir.
The right butler can make anything look good as new.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Are you sure you'd prefer not to say any goodbyes before you depart, Master Ril?
Yeah. I won't be lonely, though.
Hmm?
The people I love will always be smiling in the paintings in my heart.
Of course.
I'm ready. Let's go. Magic Knight's test. I'm on my way.
Please forgive me, son.
Goodbye.
Your talents have blossomed immensely during your time with the Magic Knights,
and now you're the youngest person ever to become a captain.
You are the greatest pride of the House Boy Mortier.
This canvas takes my breath away.
You know what, Walt? I'm gonna show the world my masterpiece.
But I want you to see it first.
Has you helped me become who I want to be?
The young master's picture magic has a unique capability.
Picture magic! Twin storms of fire and water!
It can recreate any spell's attribute.
You attacked both of them with techniques that they're weak against, and at the exact same time!
The mightier his foes, the greater his inspiration!
The young master's creativity is infinite!
I knew you could do it! Good show, sir!
But...
Ow!
Don't take it too hard. You've got a lot of potential.
But you're a little far away from becoming a masterpiece.
Thanks a lot!
Not at all, sir. Um...
That spell was incredible, Captain.
I've never seen anything like it.
Sandstone magic! Rock Storm!
Crystal destroyed! Team I wins!
Now that was an interesting battle!
Eh, just as I thought.
I'm relieved we made it through the first round.
Guess so. By the way, do you have any idea what he's doing there?
Hmm.
Huh...
I could've gone with a rougher hand on that side.
Oh, but that shade of cobalt blue came out really pretty.
Hmm...
It's not quite perfect yet.
Captain, shouldn't you be focused on the tournament?
Hmm...
We'll have to really be on our toes.
I see the young master's letting his mind wander to ensure his teammates are giving it their best.
He truly is a talented leader.
That makes no sense!
Now it's time to get ready for the sixth match of the first round!
Team K and Team L, approach!
Oh, it would appear it's our turn.
Captain Rill, let's go back.
Please clear the arena to make room for the next contestants!
Uh, right. We're so sorry.
We're working on it!
Wait...
What are you doing?
Stop!
I need to look at my art some more!
Let me go!
Hey, what's up?
Is it over yet?
Yup!
And you're up next!
Knock him dead!
Just try not to fail miserably.
Right!
Thanks, guys!
It's finally our turn to fight!
Yay!
I can't wait!
Luck, Voltia.
This contest will decide your eligibility for the Royal Knights.
So please take it seriously.
I'll be the leader.
No going solo, do you understand me?
Ah, don't suck all the fun out of it!
Listen here, you little ruffian!
Your foolishness had better not cost me this-
These two clowns are my teammates.
A restless brat and a fussy four eyes.
I smell trouble.
My gut's telling me I'll have to carry this team on my own.
Hmm.
Well, I see no point in getting mad about it now!
Let's crush that crystal!
You ready?
What the-
Who are you, lady?
Your third team member, Pooley.
Pooley Angel.
As I'm sure you've noticed, my name suits me perfectly!
Oh!
Okay, it's nice to meet you.
We'll give them a performance they'll never forget!
Yeah!
Great.
She's just as carefree about this as he is.
In that case, I'll have to work as hard as possible.
We're rooting for you, Spex!
Good luck out there!
I know you can do it!
If you lose this, I'm never calling you sir again.
Disrespectful as always, aren't you?
Just wait and see, you won't be disappointed.
Hey, we should come up with a plan first!
Good thinking.
If there's one opponent we need to be careful of,
it's the Wind Mage who's said to be the swiftest in his squad.
Second Class Senior Magic Knight from the Silver Eagles, Rob Vitesse.
And with that, it's time for match six!
Team K, Pooley, Klaus, and Luck versus Team L, Rob, Francis, and Winston!
The battle begins now!
Just, remember to it, I know,
僕らの誓いはここにあり
口ずさむ合言葉は
I'll make it true!
My song!
My days!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
My song, my days 音符を書き壊れてく
Way high climbed, it is The hat-side bar
It will come out to shine
the next day we can bringgeois's melody
Oh, oh
Clover clips
Wrong!
It's wrong.
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
I hate this.
It isn't what I wanted to paint at all.
It should be more.
More!
It's not beautiful enough.
You do realize that I'm standing right here, do you not?
Something beautiful.
Yes, like that!
I wish he would disappear forever.
Why am I even here?
It is I, Walter.
Loving and devoted butler to real boy Martier.
Captain of the Aqua Deer.
Ah, young master.
Look at how far you've come.
Black Clover, page 77.
Bad run.
Your mother is beaming with pride as well, sir.